<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[My Site]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/</link><image><url>https://winnerwind.github.io/lib/media/favicon.jpg</url><title>My Site</title><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:33:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://winnerwind.github.io/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:33:35 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></copyright><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator>WinnerWind</dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Introduction]]></title><description><![CDATA[<br><br>Installing Arch Linux may seem hard, but its actually super easy. Don't let the pressure of "Arch is the hardest operating system in the world!" get to you. Here's how to install Arch.<br>
You can install arch by following this wiki too, however it is pretty convoluted <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/installation_guide" rel="noopener" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/installation_guide" target="_self">Arch Installation Guide</a><br>
You can also install Arch by using archinstall <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/archinstall" rel="noopener" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/archinstall" target="_self">Learn more</a> <br><br><br><br>
<br>Using Minitool Partition Wizard, Partition your disk into such based on whether you wish to dual boot (Be able to use Windows and Arch Linux in the same system) or replace Windows with Arch Linux. Skip to point number 4 if you're not dualbooting.
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://kb.parallels.com/115815" rel="noopener" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://kb.parallels.com/115815" target="_self">Check if your system is EFI or BIOS based</a>. <br>If you're dualbooting, Partition it into 4 parts by shrinking Windows' partition. Here's how they should be if you're on an EFI system (The order of the partitions is mostly irrelevant)
<br>
<br>An EFI system partition of 1GB <br>A Linux SWAP partition of atleast 4GB (More is better, however don't exceed the amount of your RAM. Check the amount of your RAM in the Task Manager)
<br>An EXT4 partition of atleast 32GB. Here is where all your files go
<br>Your Windows Partition
<br>(All other partitions)
<br>
<br>If you're on an BIOS Partition, make the exact same partitions except the EFI partition.
<br>Don't forget to format them as such, but it doesn't really matter in this stage. Be careful not to accidentally format your Windows' partiton! If you have installed other Linux based operating systems, you would know that usually we leave the partition unformatted, but Arch's installer cannot read unformatted/unallocated partitions. As such, it is needed to format it. The exact formatting used does not matter, however they must be distinct so that they don't merge into one partition
<br>If you're not going to dualboot, don't make the EXT4 partition. Your Windows' partition will be overwritten in later steps. This will irrevocably delete all data on your Windows' partition and replace it with Linux.
<br><br>Things you'll need : A USB with at least 8GB storage. All files on this USB will be irrevocably deleted in this section.<br>
<br>Regardless of operating system, get the app <a href="https://etcher.balena.io/" target="_self" rel="noopener" class="is-unresolved">Balena Etcher</a>. It's a GUI based tool that lets us create an installer USB. <br>Visit <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://archlinux.org/download/" rel="noopener" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://archlinux.org/download/" target="_self">this page</a> and under the section "BitTorrent Download", download the Torrent. You will need a torrent client like uTorrent. <br>Open Balena Etcher and plug in your USB. Select the .iso file that you downloaded using torrent and flash your USB. Be careful in selecting the correct USB, as doing so may delete all the files on a used USB or reformat your main drive
<br>After the flash is done, you have an installer USB. Congratulations!
<br><br>This part gets a bit tricky because it depends from system to system, however the general instructions stay the same.<br>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.gigabyte.com/us/Support/Consumer/FAQ/3001" rel="noopener" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://www.gigabyte.com/us/Support/Consumer/FAQ/3001" target="_self">Disable Secure Boot</a> <br>Reboot your system.
<br>When the manufacturer logo is shown during boot up, be sure to look for text that reads on the lines of "Press (button) to enter BIOS Menu". Some systems require a full shut down to show this text
<br>If the text is not shown, keep pressing buttons until a beep sound is heard and/or the BIOS menu opens.
<br>Select "Choose another boot medium" This step varies from system to system heavily. Please refer to your motherboard's manual
<br>Select Arch Linux Install Medium
<br>Press Enter for Boot into Arch Linux
<br><br>Now that we have booted into Arch, the install begins. After the image is copied to RAM, you should be greeted with a message and a terminal. Do not remove the USB during the install at any point, as it may have unintended side effects and consequences (Mostly not permanent)<br>
<br>If the font is too small (as may be the case for 4K displays), type in setfont ter-132b verbatim to switch to a bigger font. This font is huge, so try to stick to the default font as much as possible <br><br>
<br>If you wish to use Ethernet, plug it in, and skip to point number 10 or else continue. Type in rfkill and make sure that the output looks like this
<br>ID TYPE DEVICE SOFT HARD 0 bluetooth hci0 unblocked unblocked 1 wlan phy0 unblocked unblocked
Copy<br>
<br>If you see that wlan has the word blocked under SOFT then administer the command rfkill unblock wlan. If it has the word blocked under HARD then make sure that there is no physical switch that is turning off the WiFi card.
<br>Type in iwctl. This should open an interactive prompt starting with the words [iwd]#. This shows that you're using iwctl.
<br>Type device list. <br>If the device is turned off or it's adapter is turned off, turn it on using device [name] set-property Powered on and adapter [name] set-property Powered on replacing [name] with the name of the device.
<br>Initiate a scan using station [name] scan
<br>List all networks using station [name] get-networks
<br>Then connect using station [name] connect [name of the network you wish to connect to]
<br>Enter password if any.
<br>Once this is done, press the key combination CTRL+C. This kills the current command. Alternately you can exit by administering exit. <br>Type in ping google.com. If you get an error like ping: google.com: Temporary failure in name resolution then you may have messed up in the earlier steps. IWCTL is a bit hard to work with, so don't worry about trying again. If it starts pinging, then you'll get periodic messages on screen. This shows that your internet is working. Kill the command using CTRL+C when done. We have officially connected to the internet. This is a very important step.
<br><br>Now we copy Linux's image into the newly partitioned disk. Be careful during these steps, as missing one can set you back by several more steps or need you to restart from the start.<br>
<br>Type in fdisk -l. You will get an output similar to this.
<br>Sector size (logical/physical): 512 bytes / 512 bytes
I/O size (minimum/optimal): 512 bytes / 512 bytes
Disklabel type: gpt
Disk identifier: 0C8B0FFB-9128-40E5-8869-2A102B375F98 Device Start End Sectors Size Type
/dev/nvme0n1p1 2048 206847 204800 100M EFI System
/dev/nvme0n1p2 206848 239615 32768 16M Microsoft reserved
/dev/nvme0n1p3 239616 797470719 797231104 380.1G Microsoft basic data
/dev/nvme0n1p4 797470720 965242879 167772160 80G Microsoft basic data
/dev/nvme0n1p5 965242880 973631487 8388608 4G Microsoft basic data
/dev/nvme0n1p6 973631488 975730687 2099200 1G Microsoft basic data
/dev/nvme0n1p7 975730688 976771071 1040384 508M Windows recovery environment
Copy<br>
<br>Don't forget which partition is which! The codes in the Device section are important. Be sure to match that with the Type and Size when proceeding.
<br>Use mkfs.ext4 /dev/[code] to format the root partition, where all your files go. replace [code] with the appropriate item from Device. Do NOT mess up the code. Doing so may overwrite the wrong partition, leading to loss of data, especially if you are dualbooting
<br>As an example, in the list I showed earlier, I want to dualboot, so I made the 80GB partition for my files. So, I'll use the command mkfs.ext4 /dev/nvme0n1p4 <br>Set the SWAP partition using mkswap /dev/[code] replacing [code] with the correct Device of the SWAP partition
<br>If you made an EFI system, use mkfs.fat -F 32 /dev/[code] replacing [code] with the correct Device of the EFI system. If not, skip this section.
<br><br>[WORK IN PROGRESS!!]]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/tutorials/arch-linux.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Tutorials/Arch Linux.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Contact me!]]></title><description><![CDATA[<br><br><br><br>E-Mail -&gt; elbowsparse@gmail.com <br><br>Instagram -&gt; winnerwind0041<br>Reddit -&gt; u/WinnerWinds<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="index" data-href="index" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/index.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Home</a>]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/contact.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Contact.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:14:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Home]]></title><description><![CDATA[<br>Hi, I am WinnerWind. Welcome to my personal website!<br><br>I honestly have no idea. I just made this site because I felt like it. Maybe one day it'll become something great, but for now it's my personal space to blog, vlog or do PSAs, though it'll most likely end up as a file dump.<br><br>This site was made with <a href="https://obsidian.md/" target="_self" rel="noopener" class="is-unresolved">Obsidian</a>, yes the notes taking app. There's a great plugin called the <a href="https://github.com/KosmosisDire/obsidian-webpage-export" target="_self" rel="noopener" class="is-unresolved">Webpage HTML Export</a> which helps me export it without a hiccup. It is then uploaded to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://github.com/WinnerWind/winnerwind.github.io" rel="noopener" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://github.com/WinnerWind/winnerwind.github.io" target="_self">My personal Github repository</a> using Github Desktop. Really, it works without a hiccup, and its a great workflow for people who don't know the first thing about HTML, like me.<br><br><a data-href="Contact" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/contact.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Contact</a><br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Playlists" data-href="Playlists" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/music/playlists.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">My Playlists</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Songs" data-href="Songs" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/music/songs.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">My Music</a>]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">index.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:59:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Songs I like right now]]></title><description><![CDATA[<br> <br>I swear I'm not Japanese]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/music/songs.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Music/Songs.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:57:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Playlists I like right now]]></title><description><![CDATA[<br> more coming soon]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/music/playlists.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Music/Playlists.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:56:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>