<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[WinnerWind's Writing Pad]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/</link><image><url>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/lib/media/favicon.jpg</url><title>WinnerWind's Writing Pad</title><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:39:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:39:17 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></copyright><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator>WinnerWind</dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Redwood University. Not the best academy to be in, yet the bored, 19 year old Ranmara Rohith had to study there. "Study hard, and get a good job, then you can be a chooser", he was told. He would have rather gone to an Ivy League college, but his widowed mother did not have the funds for that. He enrolled in as many classes as he could, which meant that he had to stay in the university longer than all the other students. He always thought that going to Redwood was not only a thankless endeavour, but a waste of his time. He did not want to be an engineer, yet his mother insisted, and he could not say no.<br>His professors always noted his lack of focus and interaction in the lectures. Day after day he would gaze out of the window, often spotting the same group of raddiwalas walking by the side of the road. Even if it was too rainy, they would walk by the side of the road, as if nothing were happening. They never carried an umbrella either; it was too expensive for them. If on the off chance they did not come, Ranmara would talk to his only friend at the university, Pharia Makhi. They were friends ever since they were children playing in a park, ignorant of the pains of life. None of the professors appreciated this lack of respect. <br>Pharia was a very silent girl, and never appreciated small talk, yet she got along with him, and only him. The alumni were jealous of their close relationship and often spread rumours against them, which had no effect on the duo, other than to bond them closer together and isolate them from the rest of the world. She was the only person who made his experience at Redwood bearable. <br>One day, Pharia did not come to the university. Ranmara suspected that she had fallen sick, not a very uncommon phenomenon in the middle of the dengue season. People were falling sick with dengue by the dozen. However, a week went by, then a month. She was nowhere to be seen. What was wrong? He called her on her number. No response. He tried sending an SMS message, but his phone displayed the haunting message "NO BALANCE". "Why did I not ask for her address!" he groaned, and felt a bit uneasy. "I hope nothing is wrong".  <br>Then, it struck him, like a bolt of thunder from the heavens. On his 19th birthday, he screamed out "I got it!" in front of his mother, the only attendant to his birthday 'party'. He jumped from the chair and ran to his room, knocking the birthday cake from the table, making it almost fall down. He had an idea, and he himself was not sure about what it would entail. He packed his hiking backpack with the items he takes whenever he goes travelling with his mother, a laptop, some chargers, his nearly empty wallet and some medicine. <br>Without explaining, he ran out of the door with his half packed bag and ran down the stairs of his apartment. "I'll explain everything to you!" he yelled as he jumped down the stairs.<br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 2" data-href="Chapter 2" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Next Chapter</a>]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 1.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Ranmara ran down the eerie staircase, with his haphazardly packed bag, shoe laces untying themselves and his phone, complaining that it is almost out of charge. <br>He jumped on the last step and fell down flat on his face, but he quickly got up and kept running. He bumped through the door, confident that he broke its hinge, but there was no time for that. He wasn't even sure what he was doing anymore, just running aimlessly. He ran out into the courtyard. <br>A group of elementary students were playing football. A kid who towered over all the others stood on the other side of the courtyard. He kicked the ball so high that made a majestic arch so big that it might have been for the marriage of two apartment buildings. In one kick, the ball flew to the other side of the sizable courtyard and bounced off the railing. <br>Ranmara, who just ran through the entrance door of the apartment was smacked in the face with the spinning ball, and hit his head on the door frame.  He groaned,  but quickly got up without a word and stumbled around like a drunk man. He regained his strength and kept running before the children could react. They were left visibly confused.<br>Ranmara walked by the side of the main road. A thought was slowly gripping him. "What on earth am I even doing? What am I even going to do?". The sun was unforgiving, and even though he wore a black jacket, he was too deep in thought to feel his skin burning. Even though the sun was setting, it was October, and the oppressive, humid weather blanketed the polluted city of Bangalore. <br>A few minutes later he tripped on a rock. He was snapped out of the zone, and stood in place for a minute before finally coming to his senses again. "You look lost sonny" a homeless man in bright but ragged clothes who happened to be sitting nearby said. "Life is too short, live it how you want; don't do what what everyone else wants. People run away all the time just to find a new, more exciting life. I did the same when I was your age, and look at where that got me.". Ranmara paid no heed to the man, but instead kept walking. His advice kept echoing in his head.<br>Ranmara decided to stop for the day near a small restaurant. The owner of the establishment had already gone home. The sun had set hours ago, and the mood of the city was slowly dampening. Besides, the clouds were threatening and it would be too risky to continue walking towards an unknown destination. He laid down on the dusty  floor of the restaurant, under a table just for extra safety and privacy. He looked at his phone, just to find something, something that may hint at the whereabouts of his friend Pharia. No sooner did he turn it on than it quickly shut down. It had run out of charge. He'd have to try in the morning.<br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 1" data-href="Chapter 1" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Previous Chapter</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 3" data-href="Chapter 3" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 3.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Next Chapter</a>]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 2.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>"The heck are you doing down there sonny?" a voice boomed from above the table. Ranmara was shocked into waking up and harshly hit his head on the edge of the table. "Look, you gotta leave. I don't want to hear any excuses, I am not giving you a job. Just get out of here". Guiltily, Ranmara walked out.<br>
Suddenly, like the table that he hit, he remembered everything that happened the previous day. He couldn't believe his lack of rational thought when he ran away from home. He tried to turn on his phone. No luck. He looked around for what he could do. The top priority was to get his phone charging.<br>
The weight of the situation slowly loomed over him as he roamed around the city, finding somewhere he could get an idea as to what to do next. He had no food, no water, no means of survival at all. He could be dead the next day if he did not play his cards right.<br>
Walking south by the side of the road, he came across a shop. It's banners said in bold letters "TRIATHLON". Was that the name of the shop, or an event they were hosting?<br>
Triathlon was a rather popular sports shop in the area. It had everything from brand new, cutting edge sports cycles, to kayaks that were the fastest and sleekest in the world. The franchise was known for renovating old warehouses into a very large sports shop. As he looked around the camping section, all stacked with gear that were tempting him to buy, he put two and two together and realized that things cost money, and he had no money to spend. How would he get the money he needed?<br>
He roamed around looking for something, anything, that would give him a small boost, or at least some power for his phone, but no luck.<br>
The sun went down and Ranmara just stared at the staff closing the place and ensuring that all the inventory were in place. A staff member pulled the rusted shutters down with so much force that it hit the ground and cracked it's locking mechanism. "That's too bad..." another staff member who witnessed the incident said "We'll have to get it fixed in the morning". Ranmara had a thought. The shutters were left unlocked, and he could waltz in and grab everything he would need! It would be illegal, sure, but it's not like he would get caught for such a petit larceny.<br>
The staff drove away, chatting amongst themselves. Ranmara seized this opportunity and slipped into the establishment. As he walked around in the darkness, he knocked over a can of MRE. This made him break out a cold sweat, but he kept looking around. After some searching he finally found the camping section. He stole a decently sized bag and a prop up tent that was conveniently placed in a neat box. Just as he was about to leave he heard the engine of a car hum outside and then the squeal of brakes.<br>
Taking all his stuff he ran and hid in one of the changing rooms. A staff member with a flashlight walked in. He appeared to be looking for something at the receptionist's counter. It was then when he realised the MRE can rolling on the floor. "Who's there!" He screamed out. Ranmara thought he was done for. To his surprise the staff member just replaced the can. "Must have fallen down". He went home. Sighing Ranmara ran out, taking a few cans of MRE for the road.<br>
Now the only matter was finding where to sleep. After some more searching he found a nice alleyway where he could get some well needed sleep. It seemed like no one has used it for a while. He propped up his tent a few meters from the mouth of the alley way and quickly fell asleep.<br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 2" data-href="Chapter 2" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Previous Chapter</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 4" data-href="Chapter 4" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 4.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Next Chapter</a>]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 3.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:26:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Ranmara was awoken by water dripping on his face. He opened his eyes to see that a large hole had been made in the fabric of the tent. He peeked outside. The road was shining, potholes were filled with water and the corners of the buildings were dripping. Clearly it had rained. Well, it was time for him to get going anyway. He thought for a bit about some places he could go to, especially for a meal. Looking at his feet he saw the cans of MRE that he stole yesterday. He had about ten of those, each amounting to roughly a meal. Ranmara's belly groaned. After all, he had not eaten for the whole of yesterday. "These must be a hassle to carry, I'm surprised they're considered survival equipment." He thought for a bit. Eventually he concluded that there was no point in hoarding these. He took a can and read the instructions.<br>
"Open the can and find the bag labelled Heater"<br>
"Fill the heater up with water until the fill line. Do not fill it past the fill line."<br>
Ranmara looked around for some sources of water. There appeared to be a pipe exiting the wall flowing with excess rainwater. It's flow was just slow enough to let him fill the bag without exceeding the line. He put that bag aside and continued reading.<br>
"Insert your meal packet into the Heater bag and wait for five minutes."<br>
As he took his meal packet out of the can, his elbow gently grazed the Heater bag. Ranmara saw that it had generated some heat. He carefully inserted the meal packet and waited for a few minutes. His belly groaned at the thought of having warm food. He impatiently ripped open the packet, revealing the meal inside. It happened to be Potato and Peas curry. Ranmara felt that it did not taste very good compared to his mom's cooking at home, but food is food. After enjoying his meal he stuffed the remaining cans of MRE into his bag and folded the prop up tent. He left the alley way and took an arbitrary decision to turn left and walk, hoping to find something.<br>
As he was walking by the side of the flyover that connected HSR and Sarjapur, Ranmara tripped on what he thought was a small rock. It's glint caught his eye. He crouched on the side walk and inspected it. It was small and round, like an oversized coin.<br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 3" data-href="Chapter 3" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 3.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Previous Chapter</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chapter 5" data-href="Chapter 5" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/Chapter 5" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Next Chapter</a>]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 4.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 4.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 11:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Backstory]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a class="tag" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/?query=tag:Characters/Protagonist" style="background-color: rgb(4, 108, 116); color: white; font-weight: 700; border: none; border-radius: 1em; padding: 0.2em 0.5em;">#Characters/Protagonist</a> <a class="tag" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/?query=tag:Story/" style="background-color: rgb(4, 108, 116); color: white; font-weight: 700; border: none; border-radius: 1em; padding: 0.2em 0.5em;">#Story/</a> 
 <br><a href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story?query=tag:Characters/Protagonist" class="tag" target="_blank" rel="noopener">#Characters/Protagonist</a> <a href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story?query=tag:Story/" class="tag" target="_blank" rel="noopener">#Story/</a><br>
<a data-href="Chapter 1" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Chapter 1</a>, <a data-href="Chapter 2" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Chapter 2</a><br><br><br>
<br>Always ostracized from school due to his honest nature. He always confided his trust to <a data-href="Protagonist's Best Friend" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Characters/Protagonist's Best Friend.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Protagonist's Best Friend</a> and no one else. She is his only friend 
<br>Texts <a data-href="Protagonist's Best Friend" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Characters/Protagonist's Best Friend.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Protagonist's Best Friend</a> and his parents very often. 
<br>Lives with his parents before running away. 
<br>Studies at Redwood University
<br>Family is not very rich.
<br>Father died in a drunk driving accident.
<br><br>Protagonist becomes this becomes that]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Characters/Protagonist.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/Characters/Protagonist.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 05:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Backstory]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a class="tag" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/?query=tag:Characters/Other" style="background-color: rgb(4, 108, 116); color: white; font-weight: 700; border: none; border-radius: 1em; padding: 0.2em 0.5em;">#Characters/Other</a> <a class="tag" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/?query=tag:Story/" style="background-color: rgb(4, 108, 116); color: white; font-weight: 700; border: none; border-radius: 1em; padding: 0.2em 0.5em;">#Story/</a> 
 <br><a href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story?query=tag:Characters/Other" class="tag" target="_blank" rel="noopener">#Characters/Other</a> <a href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story?query=tag:Story/" class="tag" target="_blank" rel="noopener">#Story/</a><br>
<a data-href="Chapter 1" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Chapter 1</a><br><br><br>
<br>Brought up in an abusive family
<br>Always found it difficult to make friends. 
<br><a data-href="Truck Driver" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Characters/Truck Driver.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Truck Driver</a> is her distant uncle.
<br>Runs away from home
<br>]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Characters/Protagonist's Best Friend.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/Characters/Protagonist's Best Friend.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 05:20:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Truck Driver]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Characters/Truck Driver.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/Characters/Truck Driver.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bibliography]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-href="Chapter 4" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Chapters/Chapter 4.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Chapter 4</a> -&gt; <a rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://www.wikihow.com/Prepare-an-MRE-(Meals-Ready-to-Eat)" target="_blank">https://www.wikihow.com/Prepare-an-MRE-(Meals-Ready-to-Eat)</a>]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Notes/Bibliography.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/Notes/Bibliography.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:21:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reason for the Protagonist's Escape]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The <a data-href="Protagonist's Best Friend" href="https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Characters/Protagonist's Best Friend.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Protagonist's Best Friend</a> runs away from home because she wanted to explore India and get to know more about its culture]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/Notes/Reason for the Protagonist's Escape.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/Notes/Reason for the Protagonist's Escape.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ABSTRACT]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The protagonist's friend dies. The protagonist now must embark on a journey to perform their final rites. This story follows the protagonist on this journey (on foot?)<br>
Maybe add something to do with goons who actually killed his friend or something?]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/! - EMPTY/ABSTRACT.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">! - EMPTY/ABSTRACT.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 14:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Home]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 A list of all uploaded stories by WinnerWind]]></description><link>https://winnerwind.github.io/story/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">index.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[WinnerWind]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:08:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>